我们,是水晶
♪ We ♪ are the crystal
战士
♪ gems
我们总能拯救世界
♪ we'll always save the day
如果你认为我们不行
♪ and if you think we can't, ♪
我们总能找到方法
♪ we'll always find a way
这就是为什么这个世界
♪ that's why the people
的人
♪ of this world
相信
♪ believe in
石榴
♪ Garnet
紫晶
♪ Amethyst
和珍珠
♪ and Pearl
和史蒂文!
and Steven!
过火了
欢迎关注微博@UUU字幕组，获取最新熟肉信息！
出品
presisco
翻译
零玖/presisco
校对
presisco
特效
压制
presisco
记录日期-7-1-1-2
Log date 7-1-1-2.
橄榄石使用录音机的习惯致敬九十年代邪典片《双峰》，其中FBI侦探戴尔·库柏也适用录音机记录
地球已经自转三圈了,
It's the third rotation of the earth
从开始进行
since commencements of a
组织融合簇的合作尝试算起的话
Collaborative approach to stopping the cluster.
我完成了钻头头部
I've finished drawing up
蓝图的绘制了
the blueprints for the drill head.
橄榄石,如果你能来看一眼的话...
Peridot, if you could come take a look at this...
在提醒我一下为什么我得听你的?
Remind me again why I should listen to you.
噢,对
Oh, right.
这里的那个珍珠表现出了
The Pearl here has exhibited
工程学方面的潜质-即使我很不愿承认,
an aptitude for engineering that I begrudgingly respect,
但这解释不了她没完没了的歌唱,
though that doesn't explain the spontaneous singing,
尖叫,边唱边叫
crying, singing while crying.
你干嘛给她那个?
Why did you give her that?
既然我们会坏了她所有的物品
Well, we did destroy all her stuff.
我觉得这或许能让她好过点
I thought it might make her feel a little better.
草包!浑身是泥的草包!
Clods! Muddy clods!
想不出别的方法来修饰"草包"了
Running out of ways to say clods.
好吧,我赶走那些奶牛了
All right. I chased away those cows.
让我们开工吧
Let's get to work.
在我们开始前,你介意解除融合吗?
Before we begin, would you mind unfusing?
这让我非常不爽
It's making me incredibly uncomfortable.
蛤?我说了什么?
What?! What'd I say?!
我们真得这么做吗?
Do we really have to do that?
她在这里的主导地位
Her having free reign of the place
让我非常不爽
made me incredibly uncomfortable.
给你,珍珠
Here you go, Pearl.
珍珠正在拆解的可能为波音747上使用的罗-罗RB211发动机（这怎么看出来的）
哦,很好,嗯
Oh, good. Hmm.
不,不不不不
No. No, no, no, no.
我说我需要的是钨-钨啊
I said I needed tungsten -- tungsten.
呃,钨是什么样子的?
Uh, what does tungsten look like?
钨(tungsten->tongue),恶!
Tungsten. Ah!
算了,我自己找吧
Never mind. I'll just do it.
我就缺某种杠杆优化器
I just need some sort of leverage optimizer.
杠杆优化器?
Leverage optimizer?
我说的就是那个
That's what I said.
哦!哈
Oh! Ha.
你是指你需要螺丝刀吗?
You mean you want a screwdriver?
你有没有?
Do you have one or not?
呃,为-为什么你不用这个?
Uh, w-why don't you just use this one?
因为那在我的可达半径之外
Because it was outside my radius.
嘿
Hey.
嘿,橄榄石,你管这个叫什么?
Hey, Peridot, what do you call this?
气味海绵体
A scent sponge.
呃?
Huh?
好吧,那这个呢?
Okay, what's this?
视觉球体
Vision sphere.
橄榄石,那是-
Peridot, that's --
等等,史蒂文
wait, wait, Steven.
橄榄石,这些呢?
Peridot, these?
触觉肢端
Touch stumps.
这个?
This?
重力连接器
Gravity connectors.
这个?
This?!
那是你屁股!
That's your butt!
哦,天啦,橄榄石,你要笑死我了!
Oh, man, Peridot, you're killing me!
我才不会呢!那会破坏我们的休战协议
I am not! That would violate our truce agreement.
不不不,你很幽默而已
No, no, no. You're funny.
幽默?
Funny?
橄榄石,如果你能将
Peridot, if you can get
磁铁从微波炉中取出来,
the magnetron out of that microwave,
我们就有了所有需要的东西
we'll have everything we need --
除了钻头以外
except for the drill head.
为什么不用幼儿园的
Why don't I just get an injector drill head
注射器的钻头呢?
from the kindergarten?
哦
Oh.
其实,我想你可以试试那个
Well, I guess that's something you could try.
她不能独自去幼儿园
She's not going to the kindergarten
必须要有个监护人才行
without a chaperone.
什么?你开玩笑吧
What? You've got to be joking.
你知道我什么时候在开玩笑
You'll know when I'm joking.
我和史蒂文可以跟她去
Me and Steven can go with her.
对,我们会盯着她的
Yeah, we'll keep an eye on her.
准许,让她老实点,紫晶
Approved. Keep her in line, Amethyst.
收到!
You got it!
记录日期-7-1-1-2
Log date 7-1-1-2.
那个紫晶和那个史蒂文自愿
The Amethyst and the Steven have volunteered
帮助我拆解这个第一代钻头
to help me dismantle this era-one drill.
这在文体上非常不愉快
How stylistically displeasing.
新一点的有更美观的抛光处理
The newer ones have a nicer finish.
你在制造更多的书呆子日志吗?
You making more nerd notes?
什么是...书呆子?
What is...Nerd?
你能造个句吗?
Can you use it in a sentence?
书呆子-
Nerd --
你是个,书呆子
you are a nerd.
紫晶,别说了
Amethyst, cut that out.
正如你所见,这颗星球非常烦人,
As you can see, this planet is annoying,
每个事物都如此
and everything is annoying.
在这个星球所有的罪行中包含紫晶需要
Amongst its transgressions is the need for the Amethyst
向永融体寻求许可
to ask permission from the permafusion.
永融体?那是你对石榴的称呼吗?
Permafusion? Is that what you call Garnet?
我可以称呼她很多名字
I could call her lots of things.
我可以称呼她"两个东西"-"两个草包"!
I could call her two things -- two clods!
四处游荡,好似她是一个草包一样
Walking around like she's one clod.
这有什么不对吗?
What's wrong with that?
她又没在战斗!
She's not even fighting!
她在-你懂的-她只是在-你懂的,像个...
She's -- you know, she's just, you know, like a...
你懂的!
You know!
你真算个宝石人啊,"橄榄"
You're a real gem, "Perry."
是的,我是个,宝石人
Yes. I am. A gem.
好吧,好吧,来说说史蒂文吧
Okay, okay. Do Steven next.
史蒂文有什么古怪的吗?
What's weird about Steven?
我该从何说起呢?
Where do I even begin?
他算某种混血弃儿
He's some sort of hybrid abomination.
我甚至都无法理解他是如何维持生命的
I don't even understand how he functions.
他有机的那部分消耗了太多能量
His organic half consumes so much energy
让他不得不频繁进食,
that he has to constantly feed,
并且他得花大把时间排泄,
and he spends so much time expelling
以致有单独的房间做这件事
that he has a whole room dedicated to it.
呃,不,别的东西啊-
Uh, no, something else --
说点别的东西啊!
talk about something else!
最奇怪的是,紫晶,
The strangest thing is, Amethyst,
你以为你得听她们的
you think you have to listen to them.
你才是那个应该指挥的人
You're the one who should be in charge!
哈!
Ha!
这是你目前最好的段子了!
That's your best joke yet.
不,真的
No, really.
珍珠是个珍珠
Pearl is a Pearl.
石榴是个融合体
Garnet is a fusion.
我都猜不到他存在的目的
I don't even know what he's supposed to be.
嘿!
Hey!
你是水晶战士中唯一一个真正的宝石人
You're the only Crystal Gem that's actually a gem.
什么?
What?
你比队里其他的人的等级都要高
You outrank everyone on your team.
她们该听你的才对
They should be listening to you.
你是个强壮的,独立的,完全正常的战士,
You're a strong, singular, fully functional soldier,
即使实际上你是有缺陷的
despite the fact that you're defective.
缺陷?
Defective?
啊,当然,你太挫了
Well, sure. You're small.
所以?
So?
其实,你不该是这样的
Well, you're not supposed to be.
等下,等等
Hold on. Wait, wait.
我猜猜,这-
Let me guess. This --
这是你出生的洞
this is the hole you came out of.
太小,太低
Too small, too low,
出口的痕迹看起来相比其他洞
the exit marks look about 500 years newer
晚了500年左右,嗯
than every other hole. Hmm.
你出来的时候这里一定已经空了吧
This place must've been empty when you came out.
难怪你不知道你该长成什么样子!
No wonder you have no idea what you're supposed to look like!
橄榄石
Peridot.
我应该是什么样子?
What was I supposed to look like?
首先,你是个石英
Well, you're a Quartz.
石英是魁梧,忠诚的士兵
They're huge, loyal soldiers.
你应该再大上一倍,肩膀宽阔,令人生畏,
You should be twice your size, broad-shouldered, intimidating,
但你只是在地里待了太长时间了
but you simply stayed in the ground too long.
你是说我是个错误吗?
Are you saying I'm wrong?
"宝石学"上讲,没错
"Gemetically" speaking, yes.
当你考虑这件事时,这真变得有趣啊
When you think about it, it's all so funny.
紫晶
Amethyst.
嘿,士兵,
Hey, soldier,
也许你可以帮我拆下这块钻头
maybe you can help me get this hunk of drill off.
瞧,看看!
See? Look at that!
你能完成正常的石英能做的所有事情
You can do everything a normal Quartz can do.
让我们回去用这个糊珍珠一脸吧
Let's head back and shove this thing in Pearl's face.
紫晶,你还好吗?
Amethyst, are you okay?
不要担心
Don't worry about it.
哦!这真是太有爱了
Oh! It's lovely.
考虑到我们将使用
To think we'd be using
一开始引起这一切的技术来解决这一切-
the same technology that started all this to fix it --
这个钻头真是纯嘲讽啊!
this drill is pure irony!
实际上,它大部分是碳
Actually, it's mostly carbonite.
钉子
螺丝
这会让它变得"碳讽"吗?(irony:铁的,讽刺性的;carbon:碳)
Would that make it "carbony"?
哦,哦,哦!紫晶!
Oh, oh, oh! Amethyst!
看这个-嗯-节奏性粉碎器!
Check out this -- hmm -- "rhythmatic" pulverizer.
那真是太好笑了!我太幽默了!
That's funny. I'm so funny.
你高兴就好
Whatever, dude.
那不是正确的反应啊
That was the incorrect response.
嘿,我做这些的时候紫晶没笑诶
Hey, Amethyst isn't laughing when I do these things.
为什么她不笑出来?
Why isn't she laughing?
橄榄石,你真的伤害了她的情感了
Peridot, you really hurt her feelings.
什么?
What?
你在幼儿园时对她有点太过刻薄了
You were pretty mean to her at the kindergarten.
刻薄?不可能
Mean? No way.
那只是...酷,紫晶喜欢的
I was being...Cool. Amethyst loved it.
她可能只是在告诉珍珠她现在有多快乐
She's probably telling the Pearl how much fun she had now.
紫晶,嗨,嗨!嗨.紫晶!
Amethyst, hi, hi! Hi, Amethyst!
她-她都不愿意看我
She -- she won't even look at me.
这让我感觉很...渺小
It's making me feel... Smaller.
你感觉难受,那也是你让她感受到的
You feel bad. That's how you made her feel.
谁在乎她感觉怎么样?
Who cares about how she feels?
谁在乎你们中的任何一个?
Who cares about any of you?!
你们都只是石头而已,
You're all just rocks,
拜倒在我的重力连接器下的红润的肮脏的土块
ruddy muddy clumps beneath my gravity connectors!
她又一次莫名其妙的发飙了
Another one of her temper tantrums.
我很惊讶你们俩能从幼儿园正常的回来
I'm surprised you two made it back from the kindergarten
而没把对方逼疯
without driving each other crazy.
是啊
Yeah.
这个小东西-
This little thing --
啊啊!
Aah!
上面的进展怎么样了?
How's everything going up there?
我很好,没什么出差错的
I'm fine. There's nothing wrong.
所有事都非常顺利
Everything's fine.
啊!不不不不!停下!
Aah! No, no, no, no! Stop!
橄榄石?
Peridot?
面板!
The panel.
喔!等等!
Whoa! Wait!
没事!我能控制住住住!
It's okay! I got I-I-I-t!
搞毛...啊!
What the...Aah!
紫晶!
Amethyst!
啊!
Aah!
没什么,一切都好
It's okay. Everything's okay.
这只是个钻头(drill:钻头,演习)
It was just a drill.
呃...橄榄石?
Uh...Peridot?
啊!这只是个意外!我发誓!
Aah! It was an accident. I swear!
嘿,别担心
Hey, don't worry about it.
我们知道你不是故意启动钻头的
We know you didn't mean to start the drill.
呃,是的,那也只是个意外
Uh, yeah. And that was an accident, too.
我们才走了一秒钟,
We leave for one second,
就出了乱子!
and everything goes off the rails!
我怪奶牛
I blame the cows.
不,没什么,一切都好
No, it's fine. It's fine.
我们会将它重新制造的更强大,更好
We'll rebuild it stronger, better.
我们会加上安全带的 !
We'll add seatbelts!
啊!
Ah!
嘿,你们还好吗?那真是惊险啊
Hey, are you all right? That was a close one.
还好橄榄石救了你
It's a good thing Peridot was there to save you.
当然,这是件好事
Yes, it is a good thing.
听着,我,呃...
Listen. I, um...
说出来啊
Just spit it out.
啊!
Ugh!
\为什么你们地球人就这么难交流?!NWhy are you earthlings so difficult?!
记录日期-7-1-1-2
Log date 7-1-1-2.
整个星球完全颠倒了
This entire planet is backwards.
目前还没有任何一个正常的行为
There hasn't been one instance of correct behavior
体现在水晶战士的身上
exhibited by any one of these crystal gems.
我得出结论-她们全部都是有缺陷的
I have concluded that they are all defective.
但我也没好到哪去
But I am no better.
我的任务失败了,
I failed my mission,
而现在我又与敌人共事,
and now I'm working with the enemy,
但连这个我都做不好
and I can't even get that right.
我显然已经"伤害"了紫晶的"感情",
I have apparently "hurt" Amethyst's "feelings",
而这不是我的本意
which was not my intent.
如果我损害了我和这里最出色的宝石人的关系
If I've damaged my standing with the best gem here,
那我犯了一个严重的错误
then I've made a serious mistake.
我仍然在学习
I'm still learning.
我希望你们能理解
I hope you understand.
我希望自己能学会
I want to understand.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
橄榄石,切面五,结束记录
Peridot, facet five. End log.
正如你所见-
As you can see --
哦,橄榄石!
oh, Peridot!
嘿,呃,橄榄石
Hey, uh, Peridot.
谢谢
Thanks.
但你仍然是个书呆子
But you're still a nerd.
我会确保将那个添加进我的笔记的
I'll be sure to add that to my notes.
你感觉怎么样?
How do you feel?
高大
Big.